<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ImportantNote on Babelibra</title>
    <link>http://lovefor.qom/tags/importantnote/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ImportantNote on Babelibra</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>example@mail.qom (Deep thought Community)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>example@mail.qom (Deep thought Community)</webMaster>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 01:38:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://lovefor.qom/tags/importantnote/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2025-06-19-987</title>
      <link>http://lovefor.qom/posts/2025/06/2025-06-19-987/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 01:38:51 +0000</pubDate><author>example@mail.qom (Deep thought Community)</author>
      <guid>http://lovefor.qom/posts/2025/06/2025-06-19-987/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;No, the hardware specification requirements should be minimal, as close as possible to the average user&amp;rsquo;s computer.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s practically like an installed plugin.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This refers to the Babel Virtual Machine&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What will require additional processing is keeping nodes running. Remember that BabelFish will allow us to manage multiple nodes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can be running a QL1 node and also a Bitcoin node, and also a node for any other chain of your choice.&#xA;And each will require its respective processing and storage space, but that will be the decision of each user.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-06-11-707</title>
      <link>http://lovefor.qom/posts/2025/06/2025-06-11-707/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 04:36:23 +0000</pubDate><author>example@mail.qom (Deep thought Community)</author>
      <guid>http://lovefor.qom/posts/2025/06/2025-06-11-707/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We focus on giving developers full control to develop any product their imagination and technical expertise allow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We offer tools and guidance to beginners, but experienced developers can develop very quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;BabelFish itself is a distributed virtual machine that runs code and server functions.&#xA;Think of Amazon Web Services, Microsoft Azure, Oracle&amp;hellip; The entire internet is built on them, and now we&amp;rsquo;re there, but powered by QL1 the first CTO blockchain ever created.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-06-11-699</title>
      <link>http://lovefor.qom/posts/2025/06/2025-06-11-699/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 04:04:39 +0000</pubDate><author>example@mail.qom (Deep thought Community)</author>
      <guid>http://lovefor.qom/posts/2025/06/2025-06-11-699/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Deep Thought Community, soar with us, kindred spirits! 🕊&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Across the vast sky of the digital realm, where free souls seek their truth, the BabelFish Protocol rises like a guiding star. We are a team dreaming of a world without digital chains, and you—weavers of code, testers of the breeze, and pioneers of this vision—are the wings of this revolution. Today, we share the map of our journey, a protocol that not only connects but sets us free. Come, fly with us into this new dawn.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-05-29-538</title>
      <link>http://lovefor.qom/posts/2025/05/2025-05-29-538/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 12:56:56 +0000</pubDate><author>example@mail.qom (Deep thought Community)</author>
      <guid>http://lovefor.qom/posts/2025/05/2025-05-29-538/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;And regarding the issue of censorship.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are against any type of censorship. You are free to express, do, sell, or whatever you want on your site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Remember, be good and don&amp;rsquo;t hurt others.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Individually, we don&amp;rsquo;t intend to censor; it goes against our values. But as an organized community, we are always looking for ways to make our ecosystem safe for everyone here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But the scenario we want to avoid is truly extreme issues, something that truly puts the ecosystem or people at risk, not something as ambiguous as whether or not you sell things.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-05-28-481</title>
      <link>http://lovefor.qom/posts/2025/05/2025-05-28-481/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 18:25:48 +0000</pubDate><author>example@mail.qom (Deep thought Community)</author>
      <guid>http://lovefor.qom/posts/2025/05/2025-05-28-481/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s important to address this not only to you but to all members of the community:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a development and research team, we focus on creating solutions and tools that improve people’s quality of life and uphold their right to browse and share freely.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Neither as individuals nor as a collective will we promote or support any activities that go against our community values.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Everyone is free to express themselves in their own corner of the internet—it’s their right.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-05-23-209</title>
      <link>http://lovefor.qom/posts/2025/05/2025-05-23-209/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 22:09:48 +0000</pubDate><author>example@mail.qom (Deep thought Community)</author>
      <guid>http://lovefor.qom/posts/2025/05/2025-05-23-209/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ℹ️ &lt;strong&gt;Important reminder&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;connect&lt;/strong&gt; / &lt;strong&gt;disconnect&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Babelfish enables communication with a QL1 node through a local server on the user&amp;rsquo;s device, and for this it makes a couple of configurations in the system preferences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When starting the app, the server starts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When you activate the &amp;lsquo;Connect&amp;rsquo; button, the configurations are made in the network preferences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When you disconnect, network configurations are restored.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;🛟 As we are in a test phase, we have added a block to close the app:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-05-19-30</title>
      <link>http://lovefor.qom/posts/2025/05/2025-05-19-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 19:01:48 +0000</pubDate><author>example@mail.qom (Deep thought Community)</author>
      <guid>http://lovefor.qom/posts/2025/05/2025-05-19-30/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The BabelFish Protocol&lt;/strong&gt;  is a universal protocol that connects devices to blockchains and interlinks blockchain ecosystems through P2P communication.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Local nodes, known as BabelFish Nodes, are installed on users’ devices and form the backbone of this decentralized architecture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These nodes expand and strengthen the blockchain’s network by maintaining data and synchronizing resources, while also interlacing with other blockchains to create a supermesh of decentralized networks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Operating without centralized servers or traditional IPs, the protocol enables a resilient and scalable cyberspace.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
